I remember how I opened my eyes
And found you in them
Like the first ray of light, like a quiet chime
Like the first thunderstorm
You are like the dawn in the heavens
You are the full Moon
I remember only your eyes
And after that, emptiness
Hundreds of night roads will remind me of you
On them I lost my love, and found it again
Just let me look into your eyes for the last time
I lost the way to them, I lost myself
And the clatter of wheels, like a scaffold
Carries you into the distance
I will get out, my love
I cried out after you
I will learn to love you
I cannot live without you
Your voice is my guide
I was the one who executed myself
Hundreds of night roads will remind me of you
On them I lost my love, and found it again
Just let me look into your eyes for the last time
I lost the way to them, I lost myself
I will turn into the sun and stay in them forever